[
  {
    "question": "What is the worldâ€™s largest land mammal?",
    "answer1": "Colossal Squid",
    "answer2": "Blue Whale",
    "answer3": "Elephant",
    "answer4": "Hippopotamus",
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rio de Janeiro is a city in which South American country?",
    "answer1": "Peru",
    "answer2": "Brazil",
    "answer3": "Argentina",
    "answer4": "Colombia",
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Middle Eastern city is also the name of a type of artichoke?",
    "answer1": "Cyprus",
    "answer2": "Yemen",
    "answer3": "Jerusalem",
    "answer4": "Qatar",
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Nostradamus was famous for making what?",
    "answer1": "Predictions",
    "answer2": "Candles",
    "answer3": "Poems",
    "answer4": "Boats",
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "In mythology, romulus and Remus were brought up by which animal?",
    "answer1": "Bear",
    "answer2": "Dog",
    "answer3": "Wolf",
    "answer4": "Ape",
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main source of vitamin C?",
    "answer1": "Fruit",
    "answer2": "Sun Light",
    "answer3": "Vegetables",
    "answer4": "Coffee",
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "The first atom bomb was dropped on which Japanese City?",
    "answer1": "Nagasaki",
    "answer2": "Okinawa",
    "answer3": "Fukuoka",
    "answer4": "Hiroshima",
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Latin word 'Verbatim' means?",
    "answer1": "Talk",
    "answer2": "Word for word",
    "answer3": "Active",
    "answer4": "Overdue",
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who painted the ceiling of the Sistine Chapel?",
    "answer1": "Michelangelo",
    "answer2": "Leonardo da Vinci",
    "answer3": "Joe Southgate",
    "answer4": "Vincent Van Gogh",
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was 'The Iron Lady'?",
    "answer1": "John Sullivan",
    "answer2": "Margaret Thatcher",
    "answer3": "Theresa May",
    "answer4": "Cristina Kirchner",
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What colour are the seats in the House of Commons?",
    "answer1": "Green",
    "answer2": "Red",
    "answer3": "Blue",
    "answer4": "Brown",
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What year did Elvis die?",
    "answer1": "1975",
    "answer2": "1969",
    "answer3": "1977",
    "answer4": "1979",
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What colour is found on 75% of the world's flags?",
    "answer1": "Green",
    "answer2": "White",
    "answer3": "Blue",
    "answer4": "Red",
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which British military force was established in 1918?",
    "answer1": "SAS",
    "answer2": "RAF",
    "answer3": "SBS",
    "answer4": "No. 617 Squadron RAF",
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the most spoken language in the world?",
    "answer1": "Mandarin",
    "answer2": "Spanish",
    "answer3": "English",
    "answer4": "Hindi",
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an axolotl?",
    "answer1": "A nerve in the brain",
    "answer2": "A multi-axled vehicle",
    "answer3": "A type of mortice lock",
    "answer4": "A species of salamander",
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Plaka is the oldest quarter of which city?",
    "answer1": "Athens",
    "answer2": "Prague",
    "answer3": "Rome",
    "answer4": "Vienna",
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Panama Canal was officially opened by which US president?",
    "answer1": "Calvin Coolidge",
    "answer2": "Herbert Hoover",
    "answer3": "Theodore Roosevelt",
    "answer4": "Woodrow Wilson",
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which opera did Maria Callas make her last appearance at Covent Garden?",
    "answer1": "Carmen",
    "answer2": "Tosca",
    "answer3": "Madame Butterfly",
    "answer4": "La Boheme",
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a Kudzu?",
    "answer1": "Antelope",
    "answer2": "Bird",
    "answer3": "Jewish settlement",
    "answer4": "Climbing plant",
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "From which country does tennis player Andres Gomez, winner of the 1990 French Championships, come from?",
    "answer1": "Ecuador",
    "answer2": "Peru",
    "answer3": "Portugal",
    "answer4": "Spain",
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which ocean is Madagascar?",
    "answer1": "Atlantic",
    "answer2": "Pacific",
    "answer3": "Indian",
    "answer4": "Arctic",
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  }
]
